Daitai [1 donna] zasshi wo mekuttatte dame, tamei dechau wa
[1 No matter] which magazine I look through, there's no use, I sigh

[1 Boku] ni niau [2 fuku] nanka wa arya shinai no yo, Seikimatsu no Ryuukoushoku
the only [2 clothes] that suit [1 me], are of the post-millenium style

[2 Zenbu] wa omae nya awaserarenai yo, gakkari sasete [1 gomen] ne nante ne
No matter since [2 none] of it matches with you, [2 So sorry], if that dissapoints you

Girigiri gake no ue wo iku you ni
Girigiri, just to the top of the cliff

Furafura shitatte [1 ii] ja nai kayo
Furafura, I wonder if it's really [1 alright]

sore demo mae ni iku shikanai n dakara
even doing this, there's only one path for me

[1 daijoubu] [2 boku no] baai wa
[1 It's alright], [2 my] situation is fine!

girigiri ja nai to boku dame nan da yo
girigiri I won't fail even by a bit

[2 onegai] samui me de [1 mitsumenaide]
[2 please], [1 don't stare] with cold eyes

jibun no peesu de yarasete yo
Like I said, let me do it on my own

ja nai to suku ni tsubureru
If you refuse it, it will all come down!