[3 Ameagari _] no [2 sora ~] [4 hoshi] o kazoeta [1 yoru] ni
[1 On the night] when we were counting [2,4 stars],

[Koboreta _] shizuku wa higureru [sekai] o [utsusu?]
[^3 A raindrop] was reflecting the sunset and [the world]

Arayuru inochi ga anbibarensu o kakaete
Whilst [falling off ^] from the sky after the rain.

Nagareru [hibi] no naka de [matataku]
Many souls holds ambivalence and [flicker] in the quick-moving [everyday] life

Hakanaku chiru hana mo fukiareru [1 kaze] mo
Falling flower petals, raging [1 wind]

Sugiyuku ima no akushisu
They are the axis of the passing day

Setsuna o ikiru mono e amaneku [1 koto ?] kutta ga
These spirits living just for a second, have passed through the great open

jiyuu no hate e [1 kami] ga te o furudarou ikinuke! to
[1 God] shakes his hand, telling you to live free

Dare mo ga hitoshiku kibō to yū tane o motta megurumono
Human are creatures born with a seed of Hope

[Hajimari] to [owari] wa [kiseki] no moto ni [DEAD OR ALIVE] mata toki wa meguru
[Dead or alive.] [Time] [begins] with [a miracle,] and it will end with one too.